On the marble floor of a memory we made Trust cracks first, a small betrayal
A mirror's edge in the heart's parade You drew your truth in silent light
There's always a cra-
Jamie's Cowboy Stacked! J-Dog should now.
Excuse me. Hi guys, thanks for being here. Thank you so much.
Um, I don't know. I think first I should just kind of look at this comment that I got today.
Oh, I was just tagging this video by somebody. I'll tell you. Kind of turncoats.
Let me see.
Jenny girl Jen Jen mentioned me a post
Um, and I won't go this will be a little drama, but it says be it as kiddies became she active
I was there when he lied saying you and I never heard you say that to him
Hold on. I was there when he lied saying you said that I never you and I never heard you say that to him
Hey, weirdo
It's like awakens show the receipts stalker
I regret ever donating to you. Play the clip. We need receipts that you don't have because it never happened. Liar and quick crime victim.
Woe is me. She wants to be left alone. What part of that don't you understand? Okay?
Absolutely, I have not contacted her. Okay, you do the same with Emma and Elisa stalking them. Oh, okay.
Well
I know, Alisa, I can show you on Instagram the extent of the stalking of Emma, right?
Where it's like, I sent her one message on Instagram.
That's it, I'm sorry.
That was, okay, I can show you that.
Alisa, I've never had a problem with, never.
So I don't understand what you're saying there.
You're just making that up.
Show me the receipts of stalking either of them.
I want to see from you.
You're accusing me of stalking.
How I accused you of anything?
I don't think so. Why can't you all just move on and stop talking about her?
That goes for you too, at Alexandra Mayer's, at IPTWikiInfo, at King Carl.
Well, maybe she would stop talking about us. And your girlfriend making active, serious
threats living in the same state and not too far from the woman's residence.
I don't think any of us would ever hurt her or anybody, right?
Any of those people, no. We are people that help people, not hurt people, right?
Yes, Bita is the victim only defending herself outside of that. She rarely ever speaks to new clowns. Okay, so I have you know
like 30 people probably the last three days come looking for scrap metal at my house
Okay, that that's not a big deal. Nobody cares about that. No, I can't if I even say anything. Oh look at
Look at this. Oh, also look at this. You know how beat always says Kathy Bates, right?
But let's go on with Jenny Jen's Jenny Jen's little little rant, okay?
Making active seriously. Okay, so what I'm going to act a serious threat. I never heard any threats to anybody, okay?
And beta has also doxxed herself. She's on trip kick telling me saying her last name. So that's it's not doxxing. It's already out anyway
Yeah, okay, so she's only the victim. Okay, so instead of what was me? Okay, what was Bita, right? She's the victim. I'm
I'm the bad person, right? Okay, anyway
Uh, um
Her side I've decided that she rarely ever speaks to you clowns
Yes, Bita is the only the victim only defending herself outside of that. She really speaks on your clowns
Okay, clown emoji and I will fly there in a heartbeat to help her against you intrusive weirdo bunny. Oh, is that a threat?
You're gonna come fly out here. Okay, you're gonna come fly out here
Am I sorry am I saying I'm gonna go go to anywhere? No, I'm not going anywhere, right?
But you're gonna fly out of here. Okay. What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do Jenny girl? What are you gonna do?
Sounds kind of like a threat. Okay. Um, okay, then it says bunny boilers Kathy Bates and Norman Bates
Okay, so she's told what you all see my last name, but not in like, you know, I've already put my last name out there
Okay, it's Bates, but you know how Vita always says Kathy Bates. It's kind of like a what's it called dry snitching
It's kind of like a dry a dry doxing. It's kind of just dry. It's like, oh, I'll say the name, but I'm not gonna say, you know
But he knows right he know he'll know but now everyone knows right from misery and psycho if she needs me because I'm stronger than all you put in one room
Try me you are all grown adults pushing 50 acting acting like this. I'm pushing 50
Well, but be already pushed 50 over the cliff. Okay, lady. I'm 44
You know Alexandra's 46 what we're in her 40s. He does older than all of us. Okay?
But we're pushing 50. So you're insulting even Vita because she's pushed it over the ledge, right?
Okay, so get a clue and life is going too far and a life. It's going too far. Let Vita live.
Is that too much to ask?
Live your life, Vita. Is encouraging someone to unalive themselves?
Illegal now probably not with a prosecute and that's the person does it and there's like remember that person
I think her name is Michelle Carter
Michelle Carter occurs this guy named Travis or something like that to you know, I don't alive himself getting she said go inside your car
He was in her texting or go inside your car turn on the you know
Put a hope at the co2 hose in the window roll up the windows you can do it
No, don't be afraid. Just do it. You know, you this is what you want or the bubble
So, yeah. Is it illegal to make suggestions? Is, you know, a lot of narcissistic abuse just going
to the radar and not really prosecutable yet? So, whatever. What am I threatening? I don't
understand. All I am saying is all I'm doing is trying to expose a little bit of what's really
going on, okay? So, anyway, that's her message. What do you guys think about that? I'd like to hear
your thoughts on that. Yeah, I know. I played that last night, Loki. I did play the Michelle
Anyway, the drama continues another day, and I know my mental breakdown. I'm absolutely fine. Oh my gosh
I'm absolutely fine. Hey, look look what I have right here. My this is my
Cats are so complete they they they just know cats are so intuitive
Okay
I tend to have my moments. I do get, you know, sometimes pushed too far and stuff.
The whole thing was, yeah, okay, well, yeah, so people say, oh, well, if you go to somebody that's manipulative, if you're expressing desperate thoughts or like, you know, very negative thoughts that you're having, right?
Something some might say it's a cry for help, right? I don't know if some but some might say. Oh, it's manipulative. Let's say. Oh, just go do it
Just do it. That's what that's happened my situation and I am going through the clips. Okay. Unfortunately, there's
Hundreds and hundreds of our I think I know where it where it is. I know I mean I know I can the videos out there
I can find it. I think it's on if anyone can help me
It's on panel verse VOD's channel on rumble
It's gonna be beat as kiddies and it's gonna be something in the title referencing me
I'm going through a video right now called
story about the person who called me himself evil and me the fool. I think that's what I'm looking at.
But it's around that time. I know Gotti was on the panel at the time. He verified last night
that he did hear her say that. I don't know if anyone else was here that day. Thing that is,
I think might have been, but said that he thinks it was in a different context. Like she was saying,
Hypothetically if someone was to do this and like and you know, so I will find it exactly. I think I remember it correctly
I'm pretty sure I got the idea of what it meant, you know
It wasn't it was it's basically trying to call some kind of bluff if it was a bluff, but it wasn't bluff
It's like and I don't know who I'm buying with nobody
Oh, thank you. Please don't. I don't know. That's what you said last night. You said, oh, you know, but I want to find the clip
Exactly. I want to find the clip. I know it is hundreds of hours. I have to go through because I didn't get it
So anyway, but if you take I mean don't think a person I think that is I mean, it's like I'm not taking your personal
I'm just saying if you just heard with the whole the whole thing
I read now I'm being called like some kind of liar stalker
I mean in case of stalking at least of Jordano, which is like not even been an allegation now
It's just making shit up. I mean, it's like what I mean, it's like and then it's gonna be some kind of like, oh my gosh
poor woman
like, you know like
She's not in some like high security, you know, condominium with weapons and you know, you know
She's already wrapped about all the guns she has and blah blah blah blah blah. What's happened to her
Okay, like six months ago. She maybe had like a dead mouse from Petco for a rat put on her doorstep. Okay
Horrifying. I have like, you know, 12 bags of manure, you know hundreds of at least probably like 50
You know and paid pizzas and scrap metal people and everything coming on property knocking in the door bringing trucks in the bag
Here leaving things made of metal here. I mean, it's like okay, but but you know, but she's the big, you know
She's the victim and also all everything seems to step up when there's a conflict with her all of a sudden things step up all of a sudden
Which makes me think hmm, maybe she doesn't you know
I'm not saying it's her I'm saying
It's somebody on her behalf because I can show you the messages
Where he's like hey and I GG ER blah blah, you know
Anyway
Okay, I understand the thing that is oh, it's too old as you quickly well
I don't know how I look really that old if I gain that much gray hair over it like not really I'm doing okay
Hey, babe, I'm doing okay
Okay
Yeah
Anyway, I don't know how long I'll be on tonight. I have like this mocha tonight to drink
I have a little, I have a big smoke in the back-hole left.
One second.
I think there's just one more thing
I just want to do real quick, one second.
But yeah, I'm getting already feeling
Not too much, like, I'm hoping to, like, you know,
I'm getting worn out by this, I'm getting worn out mentally.
I'm sick of defending myself over everything.
There's also a pattern of former donators on mods of my all of a sudden,
like turning against me, all of a sudden, or her mods,
and all of a sudden are, you know, just have the same exact, you know, little dialogue.
Right, and it's like are they how about like what why are they getting involved my like going to other people right involved in the situation
I like making no
I'm going directly to be there and she can go directly to me. No, they want to do. Oh, let's like let's get a little flying monkey army, right?
Am I sending CFF and stuff like over there where people call flying monkeys or whatever to harass anybody? No
Never
I know I have a friend and I'm not going to say who it is, it is a former friend of hers, okay, and it's somebody I'd talk to privately that doesn't really watch her or participate in my chat at all, but we'll verify that she's constantly contacted to go fight for whoever, right, and then sometimes she'll go, and then she'll find herself getting attacked, and then she'll be like, well, why am I...
Like not being protected if someone I'm trying to help this person, you know, so
I don't get too far too far into the minutiae of things. I'm just you know, I'm just trying to
Clear my own name
You can have your people can have their opinions about about it, but am I threatening any legal action? Am I am I trying?
I don't know. I'm just
I'm just putting my experience out there and you know for people that have experienced narcissistic abuse, you know
You're gonna get the narcissist flying monkeys attacking you after they're gonna just go lockstep
They the narcissist either has like has them charmed either has something over them
like for it's kind of like emotional blackmail kind of thing or or actual blackmail or
You know, it's a me against that, you know, so
You know, be this as much. She's much bigger show than me. She's much more popular than me
But you can use has to have to try to attack my donators by
Or my my my methods of monetization is like like it's ever been her business
But and then she does the same thing. Oh, you know, it's just ridiculous. Oh, he's clapping people for money
And then it turns into okay. Well, I'll clap his friend for $5 anymore anyone who comes depending him, right?
Anyway, I'm just going to make it real quick and then I'll take some, I'll read the questions and comments, but I don't know, I'm just like, probably feeling a little bit.
I'm not allowed to, if I say anything, I can't express anything.
It's like, oh, well, you know, then this is blah, blah, blah.
It's like, it's like all back and forth.
It's like, but, you know, it's okay.
Whatever, whatever.
People come into their own conclusion.
The problem is that people are coming.
They're just being so manipulated.
I can't really help them out too much in that state.
They'll see for themselves.
They'll have to see for themselves.
Right because many times I've been warned. I've been told this will happen. This will happen. This will happen with her and then
You know everything people said is yeah, we're basically
You know, you're right, but and I maybe services, you know
By proxy some kind of flying monkey or because I'm very loyal to my friends and things like that, right and so
You know, I've defended people
Pay to put my nose in places like, you know
Maybe I didn't have all the information and stuff. I'm not a perfect person, right? Oh
I'm not a perfect person
There's many things I wish I didn't do
But I can't
I can't really sing much more that but um, yeah, those people stink
Anyway
Yeah, oh my gosh, hold on now. I know where I heard that voice
Okay, so somebody I forgot but so her name is kiss my cheeks. She must have been on my discord once
Kiss my cheeks. Are you around? I don't know because I remember this girl on my discord and I forgot who it was but
She posted that song once and she's like, I love who was that I love who was that who but thank I thought I remember was kind of funny
I don't know if this video's gonna generate.
Okay, anyway.
So, it was a good song.
Hey, Russia, what's up, girl?
Hey, Tracy.
So if anyone wants to come, thank you, Russia.
Yeah, it's just been a little drama with a few people,
but I do have some great people here and you
and a few true friends that...
That'd actually know me and stuff. So I'm lucky. Oh, here's Lola. This is miss Lola home
I'm gonna turn my back screen so you can see Lola better. She's on my lap tonight
Thank you for being here. I'm sorry. I was up for a little bit
Yeah
It is a game of drama. It is a drama community. So I'm told like hey you wanted IP to and stuff like that. I
Don't know it's like I
Just because I came from Benny's right and so he was the Benny's IP to
Hello, hey, I told you I had a shoulder you could lean on for a second. What the fuck is that you all start up me?
Yeah, I know
Yeah, what was worse get like last night was
Yours
My emotions no your panel my panel
The vlogger was on
Okay
Hey, and there's a blog
Yeah, but there's a fake blogger and a fake beta on the other night, right and and so they were in the chat
I don't know I'm trying to try to say stuff
But there but it was like two people being and there were the fake people right and so when I thank you that no text
This is oh, thanks for coming on my show. She's like I was not on your show and don't ever contact me blah blah
And I was like
It's just that just really like kind of triggered me a little bit. Oh, yeah, look my friend rushes saying hi from the chat
By the way, she's like Tracy. Yeah
No, but it was over there and I fucking
blogger was had said that he was gonna go live, you know, and
Fucking so I was the first one to comment and I gave him a thumbs up
Then I sent him a heart or something like that
And then he commented, you know big hugs loves took shit
And then I waited a while and be did this
Popped into the chat once it started
I'm sitting there lurking like a motherfucker
and
See I let blogger do whatever he wants. He wants to play in the cat box and roll turds around have fun. I
Don't do it for him. He might as well find it somewhere else
I just want to say a thing that is in the chat like that morning. I was up, you know, it was pretty early in the morning
I think so I think it like it's probably maybe three or four in the morning
I had said a text and which is maybe very rude. I shouldn't but I do know she's up at like weird hours, right?
And then she said in the bed return text
Oh, she she had woken up to feed the cats and stuff like that and saw my text
It's about seven in the morning. So that's it wasn't like
You were up all night, aren't you? I was a long night probably that night. Yeah, cuz every time I kept
Jumping off blog is just I'd throw him by the pillow and listen to this shit
And then I beat a guy up on his panel and I can't stand that woman's voice
That woman's got a voice
because i'm like told to like go look for this clip of her saying this stuff and um you know it's
i know where it is but she her shows are like 10 to 18 hours long right so it's in her and um i don't
want to make fun of her voice like you know everything but uh no it's just it does for me it's
like fucking nails on a chalkboard yeah it's a little bit like a like a but they can't look at my voice
Oh, I love you. You have a beautiful, you know, a beautiful
It's better
Imagine if you sounded like her you'd be like, can you imagine how how high high pitch your voice?
Can you even can you do an imitation?
When she was a kid about six seven years old and didn't get what she wanted in the fucking store and that high pitch fucking
Scream that makes everybody want to rip their fucking tonsils out their ass
That's one of the kids she was
She didn't get what she wanted.
She screamed.
Yeah.
And you know, in order to shut that kid up,
you either smack the motherfucker in the bathroom
or you fucking take it out to the car
or you give it whatever you want.
I can see everybody just giving her whatever she wanted
because she bullied them into it.
It's just
Cecil had one of those kids
He had two daughters and one of them was a tomboy just like me didn't give a shit fuck it
You know and the other one
She had that screech
It took me about I don't know about a year or two to break her of it. Oh
She had this high pitch screech. Oh my god
It was terrible
It's like a sound weapon, right?
Yeah, it's exactly what it is. Yeah, they're doing it. There's a actually disorder called it's well
It's considered disorder called misophonia
but it's like this extreme sensitivity to like certain sounds like a baby crying or like people chewing or stuff or like
You know metals going scraping together and they have this like really
Hyperreaction to it like words. It's like it's like it's just like really they can't they had to like, you know
If they can't stand it are you froze? Oh, yeah, I got frozen a little bit. Yeah, I got that then
Yeah
Are you little grumpy tonight he's a little grumpy this guy. I don't know if he was comfy he'd be scratching his shit out
He's a little bit old. He but uh, he's interested when the low because Lola brings in rats and stuff like that
She's like, you know my my black cat is fucking me is gonna be 13 years old or something like that
Fucking cat solid shit. I mean, yeah, it doesn't look like it looks like it's maybe a year or two old I
Got it a little house, you know like fucking my dogs got the little firehouse in the living room
So I found this little tiny fucking house and I put it in and put it on a cat and the fucking cats in it
So now it's got a winner spot.
Oh, that's great.
Michael, my neighbor's.
It's got a little house.
My neighbor's built a little like um cat house like he's a carpenter. Oh, yeah, I've seen that shit
They're really nice little square and it was outside their house, you know and stuff
But then they moved and so I rolled it over and so I was in front of mine now and so do you remember the hamsters?
I don't know you're not old enough
Um, this is my makeup the hamsters and they had the tubes that you could put together
And it was like Lincoln logs except they were tubes and you'd click them together and they come with elbows and shits
You get so your hamsters and your guinea pigs could go to the tubes and back in the tank. Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah
It was plastic and the fucking hamsters when you throw oh
Yeah
Those are serious. Well, um, yeah, we, um, we had simple toys. We never lived very long.
Unfortunately, like, um, we came from back from a vacation. All the guinea pigs were dead one
time. Oh my God. Terrible. It can't leave livestock like that alone. You can't, I mean,
there was a housekeeper, but I don't know if she, um, you had a housekeeper when you were growing up.
But I was but but I had to clean my own room that you know that kind of thing my room was but
Yeah, you would a big good house. Oh, it's yeah, that's pretty bad the rest of the house was relatively
Yeah, you know it's just you know
Did you have a nanny?
well, you know in like
Los Angeles they do both they can they basically but they can't they
All right, you know they love like little kids and stuff like that usually, right? Yeah, well, Mexico. Yeah. Yeah, and so
They should you learn a second language and my parents were like the social like or there are like they would yeah
I know I know some a lot of Spanish. I know a lot of yeah
slash
Yeah, we learned. Yeah, there's a lot of words. We probably picked up
Yeah, and uh, but um, yeah, we've we had someone and people from different countries like we had a Guatemalan housekeeper and then
I was I think I was self-sustaining housekeeper and like different and then they would be the great cooks too like I've like
and like just
Basically, well the kids were always like we have always older brothers and sisters usually and then it's like at a certain time
Like we probably by time I was 10
Like we were being left alone at the house. Yeah, yeah, because then you know, then they could just be a housekeeper because the kids grow up
But they had they had there was like they had their own room in the stuff in the house and so they
So
Yeah
They're very uh, very good
Somebody offered me a job. It was some black guy in the back
He just got his corvette out and the one that
You know, I drove the Corvette and he asked me he says I needed some a live in but he had a couple of kids and
He liked me I was like nah, I can't do it and it was out there in California
It was Los Angeles area something like that
Yeah, there's a beach. It's crazy. Have you been to California before?
Yeah, my father married Lott Lizard out there. Remember her? Yeah, her husband blew her first husband blew up the crystal meth factory in Slab City
Yeah, and she met my father at a truck stop and
Yeah, oh my gosh, she was she was the best step mother that I ever had
My family, there's like seven siblings in my family.
And so there's, you know, it's pretty.
Well, now-
I didn't have parents per se.
I just had users.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, such is life.
I survive.
Yeah
Almost paid for that's an extra thousand dollars in my fucking pocket a month
I'm gonna get my whole back tattooed. You are now fucking right. I have I'm gonna get I'm gonna get the wooden cross
with the crown of thorns I
Just thrown on top of the thing with with one blood droplet coming down
Okay
I
Size of my back
Is it like the Christian cross? Like what is it? Like it's like the wooden cross with the crown of thorns thrown over
You know the top part of the cross and then off one of the thorns a drop of blood coming off it
Are you do you love the idea of Jesus and the Jesus blood?
And no, it's symbolism the blood would mean something that it's Christian. It's a Christian group
Yeah, that's what I mean. The blood of Jesus right there the blood of Christ
It's the blood it's the blood drop that goes in the center of that cross right there. It's
Well, they call themselves the Patriots something now
Back in the day
Don't want to say it you monetize
It's okay. Well, I will pick up on that one. Okay, but
Believe me, and I've got you just you can just say this out or something like that
You can just say the south and that's like, you know, that's probably like
Well, no cuz it's an ordent thing up here, too. Okay. Okay. So you're like cuz you're in the north. I mean, yeah
I mean, I was more than right
It's other heart, you know, but um, yeah, it's been thank you for being cautious about it, but
Well, nowadays now with with the king's fucking stuff going on and yeah,
You know, there's no sense in getting a red mac or even a yellow one. This doesn't look good
It was bad enough that you gay, you know, which automatically put you in a different category in AI I'd imagine
well, yeah, um, I
don't know what how they
How the AI the YouTube AI works for screening screening things. That's like I only I just like basically, you know know that
Now I know the rules really well. I know it's like I was able to go like you know months without any problem
You know occasionally I'll get a warning and then the warnings last a few months and stuff like that and you know
I take to take the YouTube YouTube school where they ask you like seven questions multiple choice
And you have to like pass them and so because I play I made me do that one. Yeah
Yeah, I got a plus on mine was for nudity. Oh, this was for nudity
Yeah, I think I think I did the nudity policy and it was like interesting quiz about like he's like well
If you are waxing are you allowed to show like a full leg spread?
Yeah, and I think I think the answer was yes, you were allowed to like you can show if you know where it is
It's categorized right now. I got mine for entertainment
You know, don't even put it for you know, you you can cover your ass if you go on to blog people and blogging
But you know, you know, you got art and you got education
So if you're gonna do something like that, then you slip it under education and then mark it for over 18
Down in the advanced if you'll notice to all my videos that stay up are all age, you know
fucking
They're age-restricted or uh, they're all age-restricted. That's it
Yeah, well
Yeah, and then you can basically show like almost anything but they don't that didn't they're not monetized, right?
Did YouTube fucking nail you to see if you were fucking over 21 or over 18?
They did it to me today. They did to you. Yeah, I was found I want the fuck
Oh, I reported to kids. They were doing live streams two different live streams
Cuz I'm up all night, and I'm flipping through live streams, right? They see kids and I'm like hey wait a minute
Cuz I got the chat turned on
They get the chat turned off and they do nothing and I work for a few minutes
And I won't do anything
But if I see that they got the chat on I'll watch a chat now see the perverts coming in
Like they fucking can smell
And I'm like now I automatically I got two kids they were two
Two kids were live streaming and that that got shut off immediately by YouTube because I went back and it was gone
Yeah
Well, yeah, they work pretty fast enough. Let's say the AI can verify that kind of thing
Uh-huh. So anyways today, I can't I don't ever log off of my YouTube
It runs 24 seven because I need to listen into a book or whatever, you know, it's like having a radio
And, uh, I fucking, all of a sudden YouTube asked for me to age verify I could do one of three things and one of them said, just turn on the camera.
They wanted either my, or the tax return or fucking photo ID, something like that.
No, a passport, a fucking photo ID or turn on the camera. So I had to turn on the camera.
But they ate for verification on me for some reason
With a well, you know, because maybe that it was like
Because I reported those two
Yeah
My oh, but if you're talking kids, you know, I mean, yeah, they were teenagers. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
That's what pushes me off because I think by the fucking AI
You can be 13 and have like, you know, or I think you live streams
I don't know that I see it cut off like it's 16 17
Okay, they fucked by them
They're not virgins, nine out of 10 out of a million fucking virgins at that point.
Yeah.
You know, I mean, they, we all went to high school.
You know, sex education was taught in fourth grade.
Yeah.
Well, our parents had to sign for that.
Do you remember that?
Did they have it when you went to school?
Yeah, I think well, I just remember they separate the boys from the girls. Yeah
Yeah, I remember I was like kind of like kind of laughing and everyone else. Oh, yeah, we all did a lot of gay going
But a lot of everyone but people were like picking so seriously about
They're like shut up like they're there. They're like, yeah, I kind of know this shit, you know
becoming an adult there. Yeah, but yeah, I can remember a lot of giggling. They cleared the
cafeteria and the boys went first and the looks on the boys' faces were like us girls were like,
what the fuck? They didn't say anything and they went back in their classroom and then we went into
for our hour long fucking.
No, everybody's going, well, you have any questions
and nobody has the fucking way to, we're like,
no, we're good on this one.
I don't know.
I think I had seen that book,
where do babies come from?
I don't know if you know that book.
It's like from the 70s.
Oh yeah, that's the talk that we're giving.
Yeah.
What went where, what did what, and what became a bit.
And don't do it. Yeah. Well, yeah. Plus in the 80s, like, you know, there was a whole HIV and then AIDS, AIDS crisis. Oh, it was bad. Yeah. And yeah, it was like, but that's like, you grew up just hearing about, oh my God, Christopher's father died of it. My first husband died of AIDS. He got to know his dad, though.
Oh, shit. 87, something like that.
Yeah, that was a high estimate.
Cuz Chris said his daddy never looked so fucking good in his life today died
He said he was no longer fat. He said he was looking at slamming good
He said he said I hate say he said but dad's look pretty good when he died cuz I wasn't there
But then I thought he bought a heart a Harley and was riding around everywhere
Now
Now I'm just waiting to get this truck paid off and then I'm gonna have some money
And I want to buy a fucking house
awesome and
I want to move back into the mountains of Virginia so bad
But I'm gonna lose so much income. I'm gonna lose fucking 10-12 dollars an hour. Oh, you got it
Maybe start monetizing your channel and you know, you know, oh, yeah, right
They're not gonna do that for a while. I had a lot of strikes. I had to go through
Well, are you getting so many so they got the nudity strikes? No, well, I had already gotten those, but it never wiped out a channel
I only went to two two red strikes on that and then I ditched that channel
But what was it from was it from you what we were saying or like the language? No, what it was is I had a mod
That was he's
He likes to be white
You know, I mean a little bit at that and he's got he does with a lot of radio
He's got a radio shows and stuff like that a radio channel
Yeah, you can go on his channel and talk about anything you want
Anything you want
It's you know, I mean anything like you know
You could get just as foul as you want on that so much
Well, I'm gonna post the link if anyone wants to come talk to Tracy and I
Hey summer, how are you sweetheart summer was doing her outreach today going around outreach and I just noticed a lot of
Oh, yeah, she does shit for homeless people. Yeah, that's some fucking cool
Yeah, but she was doing great work out there. It's gonna get cold fast. It already is cold here
I've had already had turned me down. It's fucking October
Yeah, oh, yeah, I need I I really can't really run the heater too much here because
It's very expensive. I know it. I got the same electric heat
I've been over three hundred dollars a month when it was fucking wintertime here. Oh
Yeah, someone says she just got home from outreach a little bit ago getting ready for 24 hours sleep in a tent at a fundraiser tomorrow
So, oh, yeah, so she'll be in a tent tomorrow out in the streets
Doing the 24 hours
That's my key. I hope she brings bring it bring a
Billy club or something
She doesn't need protection
As much as she does for the people there
She got all the protection in the world. You're right. You're right. I was just making a bad joke
She got all the but then and those people aren't crazy that bad out there. Oh, yeah, they're just hurting
Yeah, they just, they just, well, we had a tent, a tent city situation out here for
a while.
Oh, I bet you.
No, I wouldn't want that in my front yard.
Yeah.
No.
So, she'll be somewhere safe. She's not going to be like on the streets on the streets, but she will be in a 10 for 24. Okay. I'm sorry. So, she'll be in a 10 for 24 hours to raise money and awareness for her street. Yes. And then we have hot chocolate and stuff like that for the homeless that come by.
There you go.
They say yeah, they have their picture. Yeah, and people don't look at them that way I
Brought them in off the street for a week. I
Stay on my couch. I didn't know them. Yeah
Yeah
Somebody come knocking on my door. If you wouldn't think about like you see your stories about like, you know
There's people like, you know, I'm not trying to call out anybody but I'll say there's a well-known youtuber
You probably know his name starts with maybe the letter Q and
He um, yeah, he stayed with his woman, you know, her name starts with a V maybe and
No, he just stayed in a house that was empty. Oh
That's all. Yeah. Okay. He cleaned up the yard and everything and they had a friendship and when she moved back in
their personalities clashed
She about had enough of his shit and slamming the fucking door and he took it to heart
and he jumped the fence and then he did stuff and
Made it big and then he got him a place and a job and then he goes and wants to play bully because he's drunk and sprays
A guy in a fucking face the guy defense list to get his shit back
Which he knew wasn't there anyways, which wasn't important because you left it there a couple fucking weeks
Yeah, okay, so I don't want to hear that bullshit. Yeah, then he goes back and now he's lost the room
He's staying in now. I asked him if he kept the job
I would imagine he's still got the job and he's probably back in the fucking tent with
the guy that he sprayed because he had to go kiss his ass and say I'm sorry.
Oh, did you do that on camera?
No, of course not. I'm just assuming that's what he'd have to do. I mean,
well, I mean, I don't know. I don't, I already went to like LA or something like that. I was
staying with, I don't know, someone said sugar.
Do you think you left? I would have left if I was him. I just got out of town.
Oh, yeah, I think he did I think he like he was hiding out in a motel or something but I remember he like did that
There's a whole there's a few clips on it on trip kick. I think of the after I have to I'll have to look at trip then but
No, if I'm if I was him
I would have just said fuck this place and I'd I'd gone somewhere else because I was like him for a long time
I didn't have no way to go so you just I'm all over the place. Oh, see something on TV. Go fuck it
Go grab a great house. It seemed like he might have been ungrateful for like
No, wait, wait, yeah, the clash of friendship. Yeah, that's all it was people making doubt
And it's fun to do that because that's the drama side of YouTube
But no, it was just a classic of personalities and it got blown out of proportion
I
Know you can only it was like wouldn't fucking I had Jose here. I
Had Jose saying this and he thought he was gonna stay a fucking week come fucking son
I had already gotten up was gonna punch him in the fucking head
Cecil fucking moved over and was gonna lap me. I
Mean, oh my god fucking Jose San is there
Jesus Christ
Oh my god, he fucking Cecil gave him 20 bucks and some weed and half of his weed and he
come downstairs and I had 20 bucks and half of my weed and I said to you all set.
And he wouldn't, he didn't tell me anything so I handed it, he left out of here with
more money than me and Cecil put together and half of our fucking weed.
I was like, you little bastard, why didn't you tell me this would fucking give you something?
But no, I couldn't get him out of this house fast enough.
Oh, well, yeah, I could.
to deal with like some, you know, metal work.
I don't know, you get wrapped in this stupid shirt.
Wow.
But I watched some clips last night
and it's like the same stuff was happening six months ago.
It was like, except I was like must drunk now.
You're stuck in the washing machine on this bin cycle.
Yeah.
You're gonna move from one to another
and go all the way around and come back and kiss your ass.
Well, but that's what brings people in here. Yeah
You know they double-edged sword kind of thing, right? It's like, you know, you've got a poke to bear
Otherwise everybody's gonna end up in beat is or everybody's gonna end up at blog is well making you know where they want to go
I mean, it's like whatever I understand that but you want them to come here because you're making money off of this. Yeah
I mean, you've all you've never hidden the fact that this is in business for you, right?
Well, it's a you know, I do have like a marketing background plus this is where I've been investing my time and it's like it's an internet
products for it, you know and people have you know, so
Society right we can like buy what we want to donate who we want to we have freedom of this
We're not forced to do anything. You're doing music. You've got
You've got shit for sale, ain't you? Yeah, I got some merch. I got
To take the drama make money off of it
Yeah, I want to do like some shirts like I'm betting I was like trying to think of like
Shirts even like the trolls would want to buy because it's like it'd be funny. I don't know like so. I'm thinking of like some
Different ideas. I can do the graphic design. I've learned so much graphic design and also like just working with the AI
It makes it a lot easier coming coming up with some of the graphics and stuff. It's just amazing like
How you doing good? I mean stay on the course. You've got nothing better to do and win this here
It's gonna get cold out
Yeah
It's when I get into my game second life and shit like that. That's why you're the graphics browser that you had me download
I'm gonna see if it'll chime in with second life
Did you know your um, your
your son sign? I
Mean, he was born July years 30 years yours
Your son sign? Oh, yeah, I'm a Virgo. I'm a Virgo. Okay, so you're a Virgo. What's your moonsign?
I don't know everything said mercury when that broad wrote a paper
Okay, I'll have to look at it. You saw cock it's like he's meaning before I was born at 2 15 in the morning
That'd be a good sir, huh? Oh
Which is yeah at 2 15 a.m. Yeah, because so that's like, you know when I do I'll run your charts soon
But when I do I want to like
Well, I'll be able to because you have you know your exact birth time that that means we'll have the exact exact
You know, I can even give you the coordinates
Bucking where the planet is and where the stars were over above me as I was being born because I know the building
Then with Google it can tell you what star was above you does not you were born
Well, if you want to do something right now like I can start charts and shit
You're gonna put it put it in the private chat. You're um, you're burnt your birthday and
91665 okay, hold on let me just go to the site though to 15 in the morning. Okay
Let's see
I will go astral means I was born on a Wednesday. I do believe I was born on a Wednesday, too
Okay, so I can add you. Okay. Okay, so you're nine. No, so September 16, 1965. Okay, 65.
1965. Okay. Perfect. And then, um, what time?
215. 215, 315 or 215? 215. 215, 215 a.m. Okay. And then city.
Athol. A-T-H-O-L. Athol. Massachusetts. Okay. Massachusetts. I see it. Athol, Massachusetts.
And then I can tell you, I can read you about
some interesting things.
Okay, please check the data.
Hold on, I wanted to mention remark, let me see,
but did I miss?
I missed.
Please check your data.
One of the female, oh, female or male, female, okay.
I'm sorry.
I need to put the female, okay.
Continue, okay.
Okay, so now I have your profile.
I can pull your chart real quick.
Yeah.
Actually, I can go through something there.
They have some free reports.
And so this one is called,
Um, the, the seven sins. Okay. Yeah. Okay. And so, so this is just a sample of the, of
the, this report they have for sale, but, but this is a short, but it's a short, they
have some stuff and it says, so it says the first sin, it says.
Envy. It says the first chapter is about envy and the associated struggles. Liz
Green shows you how you can find an inner authenticity that provides deep
self-esteem throughout life. It says learning to look at the sky. In some ways
you are better equipped to deal with envy than many people because of your
realism about human feelings, fallings, and limits. You tend to view life
pragmatically without the need
for impossible ideals or expectations and you have a toughness and resilience that allows you to cope
fearlessly with many of the darker aspects of human nature. You can also, when required,
be realistic about your own limits and it is likely that you are your own harshest critic.
And then it says envy can become a problem for you because of the strengths of your particular
convictions about life. You have a strong moral code and high aspirations that may sometimes display
rigidity and even dogmatism. This sharply defined morality, even when you know you are capable of
breaking the code yourself, can make you hard on both yourself and others in terms of what you
expect from them. Sometimes you can swing between uncomfortable self-criticism.
Okay, and then it says seconds and
Okay, but then they don't have the they just do a few of them. I think okay. So here's from the sin of wrath
It says in the third chapter Liz green shows you how you can transform rage and resentment into courage and self affirmation
It says the dangers of doctrines
You may have ideological or spiritual convictions that make it hard for you to express anger
You can or you can fight for an ideal if it concerns the welfare of others or upholds a spiritual belief
But it may be more difficult for you to accept that it is sometimes appropriate
it, and even good and right to express personal anger when you are bullied, abused, or exploited.
This doesn't mean you should.
come out punchings whenever someone disagrees with you or falls short of your expectations,
but then it goes make the effort to explore your background as deeply as possible and don't try to
stifle a powerful and potentially creative instinct that lies at the roots of your family
inheritance. It is likely that you experience the darker face of wrath through threatening
emotional undercurrents or displays of aggression that left you feeling powerless and humiliated.
family life or otherwise you may be too frightened of your power of your own intense rage to express it
honestly and in creative ways. Okay and it says because wrath is linked so closely with your
family background but then that's when that part ends. Oh yeah there's a lot of anger issues
in my family. And then last one it says for you it says a fifth sin lust.
So, I mean, in the full report, like the people order, it's like, it will go through all seven
sentences in more detail, but this is a short one, but this says, the sixth sentence, deceit,
says, the sixth chapter deals with the sin of deceit and the thought and the way you can develop
a worldly wisdom that allows an ethical adaptation to life. It says, your mental gifts tend to focus
on matters of money and you may worry too much about financial gain and too little about developing
in the world. You can be too anxious about small matters that use of energy and
don't give you time to enjoy your gifts. Make sure you don't turn shrewdness
into deviousness. Your abilities
whether intellectual, artistic, or practical,
are worthy of as much training and encouragement
as you can give them.
As long as you remain loyal to your highest values,
you won't indulge in the more destructive habits.
Deceit can enter your life and your dealings
with the material world.
You have a tapestry of talents and resources
that could lead to satisfying financial rewards
if you take time to value and cultivate your skills.
But you also have a...
a quality of shrewd perceptiveness that could, if you aren't careful, tend to deliberate
deceit or at best a blurring of the boundaries between straightforward and duplicitous practices.
Use your humble thinking and communicative skills.
Okay, so that's that report, and there's one more about a psychological
This is a psychological horoscope, and it's okay, so here's this is a free triad edition. Okay, so it says your psychological type
The rich array of individual attributes portrayed in your birth chart horoscope is set as it is
with everyone against the backdrop of certain temporary bias. We might call this bias your
psychological type. Your basic nature is a realistic one and your characteristic way of dealing with
is to meet them honestly and then to organize them
until they are manageable.
You possess sound practical abilities
and are gifted with a good reality function.
And you have the knack of being able to make the best
of your resources without wasting your energies
and fantasizing how it might have been
if only the world were different.
You are a builder and know how to turn dreams
into reality.
You are not only a realist,
you possess considerable sensitivity to others
and your ability to respond creatively
to the emotional needs of the moment
combines with your excellent practical skills
and common sense to produce rare gifts
of tax diplomacy and capacity.
And then it says the character in shadow.
In this comprehensive chapter of the psychological horoscope, Liz Green provides valuable insights
about your essential character traits.
You are a creature of the earth, yet you are not content to make material reality your
primary purpose for a living.
Underlying all your efforts is a kind of dedication to what you understand as a higher
reality.
but mystical feelings alone are not sufficient for you.
It is though you suddenly discover, as a nursery rhyme says,
all work and no play make Jack a bill boy,
and you can sometimes be a little too heavily conscientious
and good in the presence of your spontaneity
and your sense of humor.
If you repress the rather narcissistic shadow,
you may find it haunts.
Well, and then it stops there, but it says a minor character, you know, nothing in life is free and I've learned the lesson of fitting into things, what you hope to get out of them and you are not surprised when life turns out to be unfair.
Sometimes you are cheated out of your desert rewards, or that's simply how it is.
Then it says relationship patterns.
Because of your, because your own nature is paradoxical,
divided equally between your mystical aspirations
and your need for material stability,
your relationship in life tends to be rather complicated.
You're likely to make a relatively conventional kind
of partnership in the early part of life
with someone who shares your desire for security
and a comfortable home and family life.
If you have made a partnership of this kind
and it has endured through the many changes
which have occurred with you.
uh and then that stopped there but so that's that that's all that had had there that's very
sure yeah but there's maybe what there's one i'll do one more for you i'm right now um let me see
there's there's one the horoscope for you after 40 years old um there's you can have that one you
can have stories from the stars you can have a career a personal portrait let's do this one this
goes more into the, okay, so it says sun and Virgo, moon and torus, okay, so those are both
earth signs, so that's very connected to the earth, you know, very, very...
Earthly connected nature, you're like, but also,
I've, you know, invalid and manifest into this world.
But, and then it says your ascendant is in Leo.
Okay, that's amazing.
And then sun is in the third house, okay?
And then it says the sun is in the third house.
So we'll go through some of these placements, okay?
So it says sun and Virgo, moon and torus.
You were born with the sun and Virgo and the moon and torus.
This is an earthly combination that gives a good dose
of common sense, practicality and utilitarianism.
worker and servant of others. Your constant preoccupation with detail makes you a very
careful worker, especially in those tasks requiring exactitude and observation.
With the practicality of Virgo, necessary tasks are enjoyed and not avoided, and the mutable nature
of this sign means you're adaptable and enjoy a change of detail in your work.
As long as other people do not violate your privacy too casually and without invitation,
you are happy.
In sexual matters, you have a tendency to be cool and reserved.
You pay exaggerated attention to detail, which could lead to criticism from others.
If however you would inhibit your natural traits, irritability and nervousness may result.
your feelings and your acts are not contradictory, you appear as a working person who can be trusted
and who is reliable, careful, and pleasant. In your relations with others, there's a slight
tendency to be overly possessive. You have the basic potential to be successful in life
because you're a very earthy person. The key for a better integration of your being would be to
force yourself to take some interest in activities that are not directly related to earning a livelihood.
And then it says, Ascendant in Leo,
sun in the third house.
At the time of your birth,
the zodiacal sign of Leo was ascending the birth,
the horizon.
So that's, and the ascendant is how others see you.
And so this is, and so it's the sign of Leo.
Oh, we have a guest coming up one second.
Let me go back to who we got here.
Oh, it's Mason the drummer.
Okay. Hey, Mason, just a minute. I'm just finishing up Tracy's horse for birth information. Okay. How are you doing, Mason?
Okay.
Yeah, one second, Mason. How are you doing?
Like, what's up?
Oh, just ignore him. Hey, Basin, just give me a minute, okay?
So it's like sending in Leo, sending in the threat.
People with Leo in the Ascendant seem to possess a flair for the life of nobility and regality.
Your life will in many ways be influenced by decisions you make, but have been motivated by
your pride, desire for power, for authority, and your need to convince others of your courage.
In life, you will act with a rather frank, generous, and amiable disposition. The course
of events of your life could unfold themselves swiftly, and a life full of chance and circumstances
rule to organize and to hold the keys of authority.
You should be aware that as a result of overly strong impulses, there is a danger of failure
and upsets in life.
You will be generally regarded as amiable, sincere, and generous person, who, however,
has much pride and sensitivity.
Ego-centricity is one of the prices of being born with this ascendant sign of Leo.
Another aspect of the zodiacal sign is that your personality becomes excessively charged
On the other hand, these designical signs grant in life a large dose of vitality as
well as a fine physical shape and a strong healthy constitution.
Willpower is a characteristic of your personality. You seek opportunities and when you find them
you go into it using both your mind and your emotions to strive for the success with zeal and determination.
You are very self-assured and you implement ideas with the self-assurance that let's nothing get in the way of success.
It would be beneficial to you, however, if you are not so candid and frank, and if you
did not expect others to act and feel as you do, we will grant you very sincere and effective
relationships in which you desire to bring happiness.
and an overall feeling of charitable spirit
and warmth to your loved one.
In your sexual relationships,
you appear as happy, strong, playful,
and even a little innocent.
You will always act better as a leader
than as a subordinate.
Okay, but then it says this,
there's more, it says this, okay, so it says,
The position indicates a generous though proud mind with ambitious inclinations in all intellectual endeavors you are firm and confident always aiming for total success and desires of honor and fame through your intellectual endeavors.
You have a desire to help others by means of the application of your knowledge. Your mind can be inventive constructive profound commanding respect and even religious or philosophical.
You must be careful not to become too proud or arrogant
or to demonstrate an overly ambitious nature.
This is the sun in the third house.
Your individuality is ruled by the sun
must pass several karmic tests of mental character
in order to return to the spiritual abode
with a richer knowledge in the state of consciousness.
Your mind strives for glory, special of social success,
honors, power, and magnanimous elevation
by means of intellectual understanding.
The path for the realization of fame, honor, nobility, and advancement lies through study,
communication of self-expression and self-expression. Your views about life are optimistic, self-assured,
kind, and generous. The liabilities of your mind are a lack of interest in detail or occupations
Venice is Venus in the 4,000. Venus was found in the 4,000. The position indicates many social
affairs, feasts, parties, celebrations, and related activities. Near the end of your life,
you should experience financial gain and an overall economic improvement. A natural lover
of country, life, and nature, you will find many opportunities to gratify these sentiments.
I hope so. That's the one I'm trying to work on now.
Okay, that makes sense for you. Okay. Yeah, it does because I need to buy a house after trucks paid for
Well, you have Saturday in the eighth house, which says Saturday was down in there
8th house time of birth because of the restraining influence of the planet matters concerning
legacies inheritance and financial dealings of your partner or associates could be severely limited
and may be frustrated by what seems to be harsh fate psychologically you're rather serious in
connection with sexual affairs you approach sex with caution rationality and planning excess
reason and thought in this direction may create some frustration and sexual matters and then
This is Moon in the Eleventh House.
Moon was found in the Eleventh House.
You should be an individual with many friends and acquaintances,
both from within and without your home and domestic circle.
You're a person who can make friends in the highest social categories,
as well as the person of inferior status.
Your position may also increase the possibilities
of having a satisfactory family life
and a very congenial domestic aspect
with the potentiality of easily fraternizing with other people.
And so that's it, that's it, but I do have all your sense because now I can drink with the Canadians and go to the fucking local pub and get drunk too.
Yeah, you're gonna go to the local pub and get drunk? Oh, Mason left all of them. Who's backstage? Let me see.
I don't know.
This is Corey.
Oh, this is Alexander? I fucking like that dude.
I don't know. Let me see. This person's name is Corey something.
Oh, I don't know who this person is.
Oh, my gosh.
What is it?
Charlie's Angels, Psyche's Angels, huh?
Hey, Psyche, open the door, Psyche!
Who is this?
Hey, you know who's this?
Oh, yeah, I know who this is.
This is St. Cherk.
Oh, fuck, you know, fuck that nigga.
Hey!
My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My bad. My
Oh, yeah, well congratulations on your starting your show. Yes, like, you know, good looking psyche
You're like getting pretty good numbers, too
I want to let you know that Alexander does anything he does is not associated with my show
I'm not trying to like, you know, fuck around with you or anybody else
I don't mind him like running around saying he's like doing anything on my behalf. No, no, no, you go you go
I ain't worried about that. That's
That's all new
Yeah, that's all news, you know, I mean, I ain't worried about that
Well, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've, I've
Well, I have a relationship with Alexander McQueen and my PD on my, like, this
I bet you do.
I saw that little video you did with this nigga, Alex.
Yeah.
Yo, they copying your shit, you heard?
Well, it's okay.
It's okay.
Jamie's laughing.
Yeah
He works alone. Yeah, I wish it. Yeah, he don't works alone. He he liked six with dicks
Did you ever see that? Hey Tracey, did you ever see that the Alex and Paige video? Oh
The music one. Yeah. Yeah, I did I did yeah, I did see that one. Okay
Yeah, I have seen that one we stressed up as a cop and shit like that. Yeah. Oh, no, but I don't know if you've seen this one
But I'll play it for you. This is okay music video. I made I think you'll like this
Yeah, here we go. Okay
Alex walks the beat in the city
under New York nights but his heart's up north where the rivers run free with a
blonde-haired beauty from Maple Country he's got a badge of dream and a thing
for a laugh caught a glimpse of her smile now he's doing the math from the
Bronx to the bush oh he's thinking real deep Page are you the one I've been
missing in my sleep
She's gutting trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say
classic uh uh I do I've always liked him he's fucking out of his mind I know well the bearded
woman is like crying it's like her tear is like milk I mean it's I don't know what that tear was
And then she has like a little bit of a beer.
I don't know.
She's like, maybe it's just way too much testosterone.
I think it's me.
Or maybe like Alex has so much testosterone,
he's like spread to her.
I don't know.
Guys, maybe I don't think it's me.
It's just got plenty of testosterone.
But it's a long story for the ages.
This is the guy.
We'll blame it on Alex.
It doesn't gotta look like Alex.
Be nasty.
Okay, I don't believe you.
You say you're new here.
What is the channel about?
It's crazy. It's psyche. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you. Did you know LES? I'm Tracy. I've heard of him. He's heard of him. Okay. Well, he's doing a show. Actually, his numbers were good for his like, for, you know, it's like first for starting out. Congratulations. I think you're looking, we're looking, we're looking at psyche. Yeah. Yeah. And I want to, you know, make sure you like.
Or Mod can post you're a link in the chat so people can yeah, throw the link out and I'll snatch it
Yeah, because
It could be good in the community. We support each other
I think that there's been so much like negativity and I think some people I'd like to really like have good relationships
Yeah
They're gonna be rude to me like or six like Sam has always rude to me and so ask
I'll tell you I'll tell you psyche you come up tomorrow. I'll venture you that
I don't you know what it's good that you're like learning about
Well, if you want I mean, it's like I think if you're worried
You know what I say I'm doing that he stole my little bitch, okay
Yeah
That's all that's all he do. You know, I mean when you get somebody mad and he get real mad
That's what he'll be a poor mommy. You gotta want to keep it new pants
But that's that's no good for him showing his pictures dinging to people, you know, I mean
That that means that means he's fucking, you know
I don't think it's seeing his ending. I don't think that big black cock. I don't think that's his no
No, it wasn't no black cock
He dropped his I guess
I think I got me offered like a hundred bucks to find a clip of new backstage like blowing kisses at me
Who that wasn't me?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Oh, I've seen worse. Okay. Yo, that was fucking crazy
I still I still I still I still want that video your second
Your second, you know the video I want. Yeah, you want the video? No, no, no, no, listen. Listen, you know
I want that video and you know what the other video I want
Well, him we're easy together with y'all talking
Okay, with the backstage one or the panel the panel you did what him and easy was together on the stage
Okay. Yeah, okay. I'll look for those
I can actually have a few more credits for like making some quick videos and so I'll make some shorts out of
Hopefully that one or
Me easy was talking to me easy was talking about that. We was on come up to you about the two videos
Okay, I think was July 4th
Okay, we have, we have Vicky in the chat. Okay, with Jay in the chat. Hey, what's up Jay, Cory,
Kaylee, Alexander, anyone's welcome to come up. Alex, do you want to come up and confront?
Alex, come up, I'm out. I'm not in time to all you know. I don't want to, I don't want to talk to
that little guy. Got no time for that little nigga. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm not gonna waste my time. We'll
You're not white. You're not white. Okay, you're black.
I'm not black either. You're not black. He's Puerto Rican. I'm purple. I'm purple. You're purple.
Yeah, hey purple.
Yeah, what purple what the fuck are you purple? That's right. Don't fuck with a purple man.
Don't mess with the purple man. Don't mess with the purple man. He'll turn, he'll turn black.
He'll turn, he'll turn black. When he get mad, you're
So you're saying you look like a California raisin.
Yeah, California
Okay, what are you a California ghost as white as you are?
The second was be the ghost cuz he too white to be a raisin. No, no, I'm poor I'm poor weekend
Yeah, that's what I figured Puerto Rican. I said. Yeah, it's France Puerto Rican
No, I don't roll my
You're Puerto Rican, you're Puerto Rican. I pronounce it like a civilian way.
We have a lot of communities like Fitchburg, Southbridge, that's all Puerto Ricans.
Oh, where? Yeah, um.
So, yeah, I know it's some of the cleanest cities you'll go in.
Yeah, that's for we get us for we can like to keep our sick
clean garbage on this street. It looks like somebody swept the
fucking road. I mean, it's really clean. I was everywhere.
It was like that. I know it. Yeah, they were they're pretty
damn clean. Yeah.
Of course, Massachusetts you gotta be everything's gonna be fucking clean. We've even got a damn long way to call it
We got I don't know. She's some island or some some yanker or something like that
And she's out there and sweeping in front of her house in the fucking street sweeping the dirt away from a grad
I was like
You know we're out in the boondocks
She's sweeping the fucking dirt out about don't you think I was like, okay?
Whatever it takes
That's the damn show. Oh, yeah, the days that were these and it doesn't voodoo right Riz are they don't really eat them
This mess with the tourists with
Oh gosh, okay
I'm getting warm. Let's see. Okay. So we'll see if anyone wants to come up on panel. Then everyone's welcome
So we can African now
That means don't worry. Yep. Well, we'll see we'll see. Oh, yeah, what that meant in that movie?
Yeah
All right, when that in the Disney movie you fucking
Why you do that? Why you do that motherfuckers? Why you do that psyche cuz he can
Yo, that's fucked up psyche. You didn't tell me shit
Why are you being a bitch man? Why are you still my bitch?
Yo, yo, make your own panel at a zany I'll pull money
Oh shit, it's two of them. Oh shit. Don't be surprised. You heard
God is your nightmare bro through me
Hell is froze over. Yo, yo, yeah, we will Alex. Why you always mean that? Why you be a asshole sometimes?
Bad noise
What'd you say I said, why you be a asshole sometimes are you asking like number one or number two?
I'm talking to both. Yeah
You're a fucking crazy
So you motherfucker
You did you like that 19 inch you pulled up the other day
19 inch you fucked up
And do you think thank you side of me on a war path of 19-inch cocks across the country?
Like I miss I miss cock head man and shit
The last thing you said not my shit, but on this niggas for the arm this nigga shit you like I pop your cherry
I said that money for 20. I believe I said that you I don't know what you're laughing. So
You have a mental block
Your bro, I'm gonna repost that video. I'm gonna repost the video. I'm gonna repost the video
Oh boy, nigga, I'm gonna repost that video up. Nah, nah, yeah, nah. Yeah. Yeah, what?
Yeah, you know what?
Yeah, Alex, I'm gonna ask you a question. I'm gonna ask you a question. If I come knocking your door, if I come knocking your door, what you do?
probably get shot
hold on my brain just scrambled right now like
Probably what you do what you do if I'm on the panel right now and knock on your door
What you do? Let's find out
What you do
I don't know what to find out, why don't you do it, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out, I don't know what to find out,
You let me know what you do. I'm like, I'm not that far from your house, bro. That ass
What you do if I'm not gonna do it?
And if I see some fucking hood I'll probably give you some money
Your bra, I'm not about myself either
Oh, you're bringing the goons. You're bringing the goons wide. Yeah, you're bringing the goons. All right
I got some for the goons. What time for the landmines, baby? This whole shit is booby-trapped.
Puerto Rico got the goons dried in the car. I got pits, patrolling the fence.
Oh, yeah? Oh, yeah.
A-15 on your bed, jargon behind the door.
Oh, what? Oh, what?
You won't even make it past the fence line, my man.
You're sure? You're sure? You're sure? You're sure? You're sure?
So don't are you talking to Alex number one or number two?
Which which one are you gonna roll up on though?
You bitch which bitch one or two
Curse me
Page has a beard
The Canadian
Yo, that's you if I do knock on Alice's dog, you know, you want to take some beer?
Speak speaking of knocking on doors was your boy easy
No, so go on the topic. I don't know. I don't know bro
You know what I mean? You need to
action.
I hear you sniffing, bro.
Where, where, where your boy,
Eli?
That's your boy. I'm not the one to screw you fucking cock. You're the one who's a fucking cock
Power over you like
Y'all you stupid money
No, I saw the picture of you in between Bruno and Eli and I'm like, why does he look like a 13 year old Ethiopian?
13 year old Ethiopian you look like with a Yankee hat on.
The picture makes everything take that view.
Yo, hold on, hold on, hold on, Alex. Fuck that, we arguing with you. Fuck that shit.
I'm going to give you chicken bro I'm going to give you chicken. I'm going to give you
I'm going to give you chicken bro. I'm going to give you chicken bro. I'm going to give
Oh, Alex, don't make me look like Bruno, oh.
Jesus.
Yo, Alex, you know what?
Fuck Tay-Tern.
Stay-Tern, you suck my dick from the back, you fucking white
motherfucker.
Are you talking about Alex number one in the pool right now?
Yo, yo, no, I'm not talking to you, Alex.
I'm not talking to you.
Your name is not Tay-Tern.
No, it's Alex there.
There's two of me up here.
No, I'm not talking to you.
Alex said.
Yo, I'm not talking to you. I'm not talking to you. What about the other state yo stay turn we caught that bitch
That's how it doesn't Alex. They give me give me yo stay turn. Give me all that views nigga
We caught that bitch
You're her
Wanna wanna wanna wanna wanna wanna call for my Alex number one
Wanna wanna wanna wanna wanna be state turn wanna wanna wanna wanna be state turn
I don't think so. No. So, yo, LES has gone crazy. Me and I, we've got to do something. We'll be back though.
I'm a psycho, I'm a psycho, motherfucker.
Me and Alex will be back Alex one and two. We'll be back
They're gonna form up. He don't want he don't want mom. He don't want mom psyche. No, you already done that the psyche
It's that would be too old
You're gonna try to do it twice
Yes, he will yes, he will know you don't know you know Alex you know Alex you know Alex
Alex have you right back? Let me go look for dick. They put and post
Happening yo
Shout out yo, yo Alex fucking crazy, yo. Oh my god last night was fucking so funny
But nah, I won't you know that that ass I won't I won't let Alex in my family
Sorry my doors is closed for him
Nah, I let him, I let him in, like maybe once, once or twice, I let him in.
Yeah.
We had a good, me and him had a good conversation.
I let him in once, you let him in every time.
No, I let him in, but me and him had a conversation, but the last time I let him back up, he did what he did, he ain't coming back.
He blocked, he blocked for my shit.
now I got the door I got the door you don't got the keys for my daughter you
come up with backup I can't I can't front Alex not a bad car
He's a dickhead, but I wish I was with him
Yo, he be on the nice guy shit, and then sometimes to be an addiction guy like yo fuck that in poem on this nigga
Cuz I don't fucking like him
You're
Y'all I wouldn't do that to somebody bro. I wouldn't I wouldn't never do that. I've never done it to my own channel
But I've never I wouldn't I wouldn't I guess I did I did it to Sandman's channel. Oh
I didn't mean to
I swapped up. I didn't mean to I was I was
Coming out of water bed, and I was on Sam's panel, and I thought I was firing off in my closet
To put on my jeans, you know
Hey grab my jeans when I didn't know my ass was hanging out the fucking closet
Oh
You show your white eyes. Oh, yeah. Oh, I'm sure too. Yo
Oh hell yeah, I ripped the pillow the pillow had tassels on it and I made
Yo, that's crazy. Oh, yeah, I've everybody seen every book tattooed it I got
Fuck it juice
No
I'm not that far from Alex
No, you probably not. No, I like I thought I was you want me to knock on the door like a borough
Now I wouldn't I wouldn't start a show don't knock on the store. Yo, let's go. Let's go hang out
Let's hang out and drink some beers. Fuck it
Yeah, yeah, I don't drink I don't I don't I don't drink I don't drink now. I don't do coke either
Hell fucking no
Hell fucking no, I'll show you you have we are so weird
Bad jokes, no, that's that's a bad drugs. No, no, no, no. No, I'll just stay with my we in my liquor
Yeah, and they see I don't drink liquor
I don't like I don't drink I don't drink I don't drink beer. I drink liquor. No, no, I don't drink
I don't drink very good. I don't drink beer. I drink liquor straight liquor with coffee
You know, I'm a fucking brother does that but he drinks his liquor
I put my liquor I put my liquor in my coffee and I guess keep on drinking fire. They did that
He was so I get drunk so I get real drunk and then and then flip out on everybody
I had so I carry a fucking I got the dock side. I got the dock side coming out on me. You know me. Oh, do you?
Yeah, yeah, people call
Yo, people call me the psychopath. Yeah, I've been the fucking receiving in the you psychopath motherfuckers. Yeah
It ain't cool to be a
Nah, listen, listen, listen, listen. Nah. I'm only a psychopath in youtube. Yeah
All right
Yeah, I get drunk and I turn to a psycho fire. Yeah
But the same way out though, you know, I'll be honest the same way I act on YouTube is the same way I act in real life
Basically, I can say the fucking same
Yeah, I can say that I'm the same doesn't matter grocery store fucking church
You know, I
Yeah, I'll be on the panel and I see somebody I know I'll curse them up and I'll say the same shit what I say here
I'll say to them
Why if I wash my hands of you, I don't want you you don't have a name you don't exist in my
Y'all don't got a name a low life
No low light low light people like that. I just did
No, no, no, I don't I don't go to the channels. I don't watch your shit. I don't interact what what because I'm not into that drama shit
Oh, where you know, I mean I ain't got time for that
I'm here
You want to get drunk behind?
Yo, you look look look like you want to get drunk get high and get the freak on I treat you
You try to get the freak on
No, no, no, I don't freak out
You crazy you paid you pay for sex Wow, of course I did why because that's what I wanted
I wanted to why why you want why you
Why why you want why you wanted to pay for sex for you'll just go to the bar and get some sex
No, I don't do that. Yeah. No, I don't do that. I'll hurt you. Yeah. No, what?
Why you want hurt? Why you want hurt person?
No, because I don't have friends with benefits.
That this is complicating.
What?
Why would I want to fuck my friend?
Nah, yeah.
I don't want to wake up next night, motherfucker.
I know who he's been kissing.
Okay, I know where his dick's been.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I don't get...
No, I haven't had sex in 15 years.
15 years?
Yeah.
I'm just turned 60
Well, now you just you just
No, no, no, I don't know I don't know man like guys like Michael Glomans. I don't know Alex will like you
Alex you out of something though
Oh Alex. Oh, he loves me and he might he might give you the pookie pookie. Yeah, he knows his pookie pookie
He'll show him the other end he ain't seen before. He doesn't want to do that.
Yeah, he said he said he said he said he said he wanted to do the pookie pookie to you.
No, he has more. No, he's cool with me.
You know, he said, he wanted, he wanted, he said, he told me, he told me he wanted to do the boogie poogie.
No, I'm not one of these free colleges.
Yeah, yeah, he said, he said, he said, he wanted to do the boogie poogie.
All right, he can make you shit up because you don't like it.
No, I can make you shit up.
Yeah, he did he did he did so we he did well I should be on it shouldn't I yeah you should be on it
I mean I mean you know fucking he said he got a he said he said he said he said he got a 19 he said he got a 19
19 it's for you you're
Really? No, 19 inches. Yeah, he said 19 inches with that. He said he'll poke you in
Yeah
That's what Alex will do fucking little broads. We get tired board
You talking to fucking, you know, like holes in the party. No, what do you know?
He say he's boy. He say he's gonna wet wet it
He's gonna wet it and then boogie boogie die. No boogie boogie with 19
You can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you
You're crazy. You said, yo,
that won't fit. That won't fit.
It's a freebie. What the fuck?
No, I ain't interested in that shit.
Now, I'd be willing to pay to see it.
What? Oh, hell yeah.
You remember the bobbitt where the guy got his dick cut off a long time ago?
Nah.
What was it? Something bobbitt? It was back in the fucking 80s anyways.
The guy got his dick cut off, his wife cut it off because he was cheating.
Well, the sheriff found it on the side of the road and they sold the motherfucker back on
They had him down here on the local strip joint on route 20 and everybody paid fucking $20 going there
See that man's dick and it's still worked
He made a fucking killing that I used to work in
Yeah, yo psyche. I'm out. Yo psyche. I'm out of here, bro. I see you. I see you all your hell yeah
Yo, make sure baby. Yo, make sure make sure Alex top you up real good. You heard
He's gonna make that wet you're not done gave that away. No, you don't give you that wet
He's gonna wet it he's gonna wet it up you gonna spin on it
Dreaming about that dick
Yes, you know, I wouldn't even
pay for that. Yes, you will.
Don't lie. You just said you
will pay for it. You say,
yo, yo, you say, you say, you
will pay for it. You say, yo,
I will take a pay. I will pay
for it. That's what you say.
All right. If it comes to my
house and it just wants so I
could see it. Yeah. I bought
I bought every come knocking
your door.
But I say yo, but no listen. He's not on your door. He's not on your door. He's not on my door. Yes
He said you're not on your door, but naked and he said you want this mommy
You got the big jacket, but you know you want it mommy
I've got the handcuffs and fucking two six-inch whoops or six fucking foot whips
You wanna whip his ass
Well, yeah, I mean if he's into it. Oh
I got the handcuffs and the toe. Yo, you one of those little freaks. I got a waterbed
What the fuck?
You got figure. I was born in 65. That's the old school the waterbeds the old school
I got a queen size waterbed in there. What the fuck Alex you gonna have fun
You don't have fun. Well, Alex you got the water bed is like a beach. No
It's like wait for that's an oddity
I know you better one of the guy
Where it hung down to his knees and that was in the gay violin shower
Yeah, yo, I used to be my son's fucking boyfriend, believe it or not. I told what hope you weren't a bottom. Oh
I gave that kid 20 bucks what you did with that what you did with that
My son. No, I'm talking about you. You swallow it. Why would I? No, it was gay.
It don't matter. It was. You got a dick. You got a dick. You might swallow it. No, you don't.
No, we didn't get it. They've had it up people's ices. I don't want to back it. It's been up somebody's
ice. Sorry. Psyche. Yo, yo, Psyche. I'll cover some, I'll cover some wrong. Yo, I have a good one, Psyche.
Have fun with your panel man. See you there. It's nice meeting you. Thank you for thank you for having me up here psyche
Oh, no problem. I want to show you crazy. I want to show you something hold on what you got. I
Got something. I just this is the breaking news. Let me see. This was I was disgusted on a show by all the blogger and
Somebody else. Let me see. Oh god. I knew this was coming
Okay, let me see I just had it on my
Yeah, blog has been streaming for the last what 24 hours in and out
Okay
Well, we'll see how this goes um share screen
I'm gonna get holidayed again for being up here
No, you'll be fine, you'll be fine.
Why can't Kevin shit?
He's gonna ask for another divorce.
He asked me for a divorce, they said I'm not paying power money.
Fuck that shit.
Go to another browser. Let me see. Um, shit. Okay.
If I put this there, okay, that's my link to the show.
Okay, I'll figure this out. Um, okay. Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
It should be that high.
Is that gonna share my screen? Share entire, just like window or screen. Okay, select, I guess my whole screen.
Yeah. Okay. Allow.
Then I go. Okay. Um.
There do you see it? Yeah, did them do you see them? Yes?
We both got we both got sexually harassed. Yeah, I say me too me too
Yeah, I swear to God, like he begged me to let him suck my dick.
Yeah, I dropped the beer, baby.
I did.
It was just me, Ron, and Sandman, and then that fucking loser joined, and then all hell broke loose.
He was like, listen, all right, my chat's fucking trolling me, but like, bro.
He kept saying how like I kept saying how you want to suck my dick and I was like, all right, then
Bag me bag me to do it. And then like the motherfuckers literally just bagging me
But he literally did we me and fucking blogger were victims to sexual harassment
That's all bad.
It was weird, bro.
It was very weird.
And then I was like, uh, where are we going?
Where are we going?
You literally asked him to beg for it.
And he wanted to see if he would do it.
Literally.
Yeah.
And he did it.
It's weird.
He was being weird.
He was
I've joined I've joined Sykes panel like two times and like
He's like all the I'm not letting you on unless you send
i was like hell no look at i'll show my balls and i'll show my dick to be funny
but i'm not gonna show my balls and get to a gay guy
oh come on allie
he worked the night and i had forgotten
what did he do to you vlogger
I just more like kind of weird manipulation type shit and like but no, I think I got an easy job
I really did but I was nothing too bad. I don't think honestly nothing that I can really say
Well, I'm just way better looking than you
You know man ain't gonna fall for this shit.
It seems like, like how to talk about it.
I'll do anything about it.
Hell no, bro.
Block is smarter than that.
This didn't really happen like that.
I think we were on a week or on a Friday or on a Saturday.
Hell no, bro. That motherfucker is tweaking even more.
That motherfucker is weird, bro.
Hello, everybody.
It's not even that easy.
Yeah, it's something.
No, it's all good.
It's all good.
I mean, like, in Minecraft,
he's getting, like, a spike in his skull.
Yeah.
He's crazy.
He's going to get a spike in his skull.
That comes from sites like Orbit.
Really.
That's good.
You know boys will be boys
Like you know what's crazy is Sandman can't go live without reacting to people's videos
He's probably gonna react to this video clip tomorrow
Tomorrow here
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
What do we do? What do we do is not a click where he's a reaction story. Yeah reacts. Yeah
blogging on
Shit
Yeah, it's terrible
I'm sorry about that. I don't know because they were talking about psyche and psyche fucking hit
Or blogging it with bloggers like nah, man. He's not
I just I just thought I was just some tags in it or something like that and it says they're talking about psyche
So I just yeah. Oh, yeah
Yo boys will be boys when they get to drinking
Well, I mean, they didn't really say anything that bad. I mean, that's a
Show me his balls unasked for several times. Okay, and then he said
Joking and so I was trying to troll him because he's like such a troll, right? And he's like look I even made him speechless
I mean Jesus Christ. Yeah, no, all these always been like that trouble
I mean
Yeah
Alex Pages of the beard begin again. Yeah, I will I'll get another beer
No, I said page has a beard page has to be I thought you should get
Psycho Roni's can you drop the link so I can come up with my other thing cuz this one's dark. Yeah
It's gonna be echoes and all type of shit
That's okay, I have a new video about some firm from here
Hope you guys like let me see some it's just just take a couple minutes
But uh, how did you get asked the new clip the new?
link oh
see
My gosh, my phone is buzzing. Okay. Um, it was warm in that
Okay.
Alex, are you there?
Or is Alex trying to come back up here, let me see.
Oh, here he comes.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Thank you, Tracy.
See you again very short soon.
Okay.
Little butter, little butter, I think.
So the government's shutting down, let me see.
There's a UFO family, let me look at something with my phone.
Okay, so I'm about to play a video.
the
Don't know what that is
No, there's pigeons everywhere in New York, and they're awesome the pigeons. They don't even they have attitude
They don't even move bro. You gotta like ask them to move you have to like kick them out of the way here in New York
Those pigeons are so used to people is the funniest shit
But the other day I saw three dead ones like together still fresh
And everyone's asking me why do you think that is and I don't know
Okay, have a video.
The silence comes
Yeah lava, that's crazy lava
That's probably the highest possibility actually
Or there's a pigeon serial killer on the loose
Maybe I'm the serial killer.
Ha ha.
And I told you guys.
You ever think of that, Slava?
Maybe I killed him and then filmed it.
Who knows what the fuck happened to the three little kids oldie?
Panels hum and the chaos spins
Lenor hisses, the mic's all cracked
The spirits log in, there's no turning back
Old guests crawl out of the digital grave
Cloud chasing ghosts with drama to save and die
Father Scythe, the cat daddy of doom
Light a candle in the live stream, too
In the chat they chant my name
Typing hail while they play their games
All I curse is coins, every donor feeds the n-
Just appear, whispering gossip in my ear
They fight, they flirt, they rage, they cry
It's content, golden reasons, why?
Beat us pan for guards, the gate
Alexandra laughs, we sealed our fakes
Someone's mic peaks, the lights all fade
We dance with demons, we are ourselves men
Algorithms taste the fear, they feed the clips for all to hear
God has sent my shield Scorpios emperors and my destiny
Hey Syke. Can you hear me?
Hello? Yeah, how are you doing? I'm sorry. I'm okay. How are you doing?
I'm good. I was just trying to get for one more thing to play. Let me see.
Yeah, go ahead. Even to say hello.
I don't know, it eventually knocked me out.
This vape is so strong.
Let's see, I know I had this like,
oh, maybe it's here?
Oh, one second.
I think it does, maybe.
Fairway, sun in her hair, maple leaves falling.
She don't seem to care.
She lines up a shot, swing, smooth, no range.
That's my canadian darling that's prairie page
That's prairie page
Cards on the table and sense in the air
Tarot spread open she reads like a prayer
from the Rockies to the lakes her life to fly
The spark in the flame
But actually there's like my, like my Savian symbols
and my horoscope, some of them are about like,
oh, well, you know, some of them is about
these immigrants coming into the country
and another is about like a flag with a leaf on it
and stuff, and so then it can generate this image of like,
I wonder if I still have it, but it's like,
but it's like they're like marching with a Canadian flag
and it's like, it looks like, oh yeah, that's so funny.
Well, all the Maple Leafs that it shows in these videos
looking yeah they're not not too accurate well I don't know I guess yeah I've not seen any like
those anyways mm-hmm well I got a new game today it's on it's on I think it's called devour or
something like that it's on um it's on beat it's like a VR game on steam it was like from 50% off
this week or whatever and so I was like okay I'll get it looks it looks it's like highly rated and
it's supposed to be scary and stuff it looks like there's like a scary clown on the front of it
I love scary clowns, of course, but what you're going to try it, you're going to try it on
stream.
Wait, what's going to happen?
I probably can't.
Oh, here's the period page for now.
I hope this is the real page, let me see.
Yeah, be careful.
Yeah, so one second.
Here we go.
Well, hello.
Hello.
Okay, it's the real page.
That's another real page.
Drop this person.
Immediately.
Kick, kick, kick.
You're Canadian you're supposed to be on my side and you're my friend you jerk. Oh, no, it's a two Canadians against me
That I need somebody like American up here, please. Hey, hey, you got the evil eye. You're totally fine
That's how you want to look at it or the blue bullseye
Yeah, it looks like a lot of interesting things like yeah
Like there's also these conceptions of the earth like the ethers like and it's like this round thing with like 30 circles
Oh, here's Lola
Excuse me, I couldn't get to the mute
Well, if I turn up my AI or my green screen a little bit
My stargazer
Hi stargazer. How are you? Oh, yeah, so it's been
More calm day. I'm glad I got the weed last night. That was probably good for me
I was like, did you get the week after because I remember you were waiting for it. So yeah
11 p.m. Like that we got here and then it's like I was able to run up and take pay with cash up and stuff and
I have to
No, yeah, oh my gosh, you know, I have to have a a
Prescription just to be 18 years old. I think or 21 or something. No, I know I know it's legal. Like I buy it everywhere
I'm just saying that fucking like Ross to poncho. We're an Xbox play and living in their mom's basement guys
I've got out of business long ago, but like I'm just saying that we don't I don't get delivery here
But you said prescription right so that's just that's different at least up here in Canada. It is because
You don't need a prescription to grab it from the weed store.
Oh yeah, well there's some states where in America where it's still illegal like where they don't
they have no dispensary. But the places it is it's like there's some medical state I mean it's a
lot I think some individual states pretty much but it's like California they started medical stuff
and then it's like a few years ago they said okay well it's just they did a proposition or something
as it was 18 or over for people to use and stuff.
The point is up here, you don't need a prescription to buy it from the wheat store,
but you can get a prescription for it, and with that prescription,
you can order from online places, and they do deliver to you.
Even if you can at a page.
Yeah, you have to look it up to Canada.
I mean, we're looking up on like the Google.
Oh, it's like, I just meant like, I live in the middle of fucking.
Yeah, you live in the middle of nowhere.
Nice smile on, are you my cousin?
So like, it's fucking different, right?
They're gonna have Amazon drones delivering everything soon.
It's like, then it's like, that'll be the, that'll be the end of it.
Yeah, true enough, eh?
Yeah.
They are
Yeah, the Amazon doesn't deliver like 24 hours to you. Yeah, if you're all yeah, if you have their
Yeah, I mean that's the thing like I I live in the suburbish area, but
Like I mean, you're not even close to anything like that. So yeah, for me, it's just normal
Like most Americans idea of Canada, like I pretty much lived that in that part of Canada. Yeah
Well, if you'd like your video page or is it you've seen it before I know her
Absolutely love the second one of the first one's fucking hilarious. I like it too, but she's like it's like I just turn into a trans
Like I go for a fucking transition
I like tie you up put you in the closet and like and like
Yeah, because you drew it on when you put it in the closet and tied me up.
Well, I don't know.
That was kind of a creative idea.
Oh good for you Stargazer, that's cool too.
I know it, driving, like having to go the long distance to just take care of like regular things.
I know that's a pain, but my God, living that remote, like so far away from other people.
Wow, I love that love the idea. Anyways, I mean I like it if I were actually
It really is most best this is give and take to it, but you know what I'd choose this any fucking day
Oh, if I had that like always again over and over. Yeah, for sure
God he doesn't think you're real age
Gotty, how come why don't you think I'm real? Hey Joe like a hundred million times
No, he thinks you're a clone.
Like, I mean, he thinks you are real,
but he doesn't think you're the original page.
Let me put it that way.
Oh, no, that's like a disorder that's like that's like similar to the sort of Alexander has where he thinks everybody's like the same person like but it's like
It's like more like cold paranoia
Yeah, yeah paranoia, but it's like I mean there are people that will alter accounts and it's like who knows who could be who are under what like what
You know, it's like really easy all it is is like a little screen name, you know, and you can
No, I care to do it. This is me. You know it is
Yeah, we don't know you're just saying it we don't know I know
I know. Paige, I'll play it.
You're gonna have to show your feet for Alex.
He's the only one that has proof of the original page.
Paige, I don't know if you saw it.
I ain't putting my feet up here unless y'all pay me.
I'll look for this page.
I was saying I almost had it for you, man.
Almost.
Let's see this page.
Oh, well, I played this the last time, you know?
I remember, I think I wanted to play one.
Let me see, but that's a good one too.
Are you there, Paige?
Let me see.
Yeah, I'm still here, I'm listening.
Okay, you're listening, I'm like, I'm sorry.
Let me see, do you, it's one?
No, it's not one.
Really?
Um, okay, I'm sorry
See this is what this is what weed does I get so stone you guys you guys talk
Why would I want to talk to her do you you see how she talks to me
even now. Your name burns behind my eyes. Yeah, it's nice, God. Three full goddess,
mother of disguise, through obsidian.
I'll hide with you.
Oh, it's okay.
Well, that's not okay.
What kind of person would I be if I just left in the middle of a song you made for me?
I couldn't fuck.
Of course, I wouldn't leave.
No, that was really nice, and then you put quite a bit of time into this stuff, too,
so thank you.
Oh, you're welcome.
Glad you enjoyed it.
I'm sorry.
You guys talk.
Always thrusting us into the limelight.
I felt like I was just a kid into trouble with like my sibling.
You guys sit here and you talk.
Yeah, really?
So what's up with you, Paige?
You're doing your painting this evening?
How did you know?
Because you said earlier.
That's what you said you were doing.
It was probably in chat.
I think you said it in chat.
It was a little bit.
I guess you're just smart, and I'm dumb.
I forgot.
Are you doing the, um.
The the emotional transfer stuff yet. Have you started on that or it was actually just going to start that right now?
Because I thought you know what that'd be quite interesting and I had a huge huge nap today
And so probably gonna be up for a while
Nice. Yeah, I got nothing else to do
What size painting are you doing like how long do you figure this would take?
Well, okay, so this one I'm gonna do for a frat,
well, I don't know yet.
I'm just doing it and like the inspiration is
for my friend's Bear Ass Walls with this really nice house.
I'm like, every time I go over there,
I'm like, fuck, it's like my vacation home,
but it's also like, what the fuck do I look at?
You know, and it's so neat and tidy and perfect too.
So I'm like, I need some crazy color chaos.
And honestly, I was just gonna go with the flow,
but I guess the color palette will be like kind of,
I was thinking because for him, for that person, if it was a commission, it'd be like, you know, greens and blues and shit like that.
But I feel like if I just go with the flow tonight and I do that picture tomorrow, then I can, uh, I don't know.
Anyways, it'd be fun to do the energy thing.
Okay, well, let's rewind.
My question was how long would it take you to do a painting like this?
Not long. It's fluid art, so it takes no time.
Excellent.
Are you high page?
Am I high time was talking to all man. Look these guys are talking about fucking someone wearing
Ladies long and I thought they were speaking about psych, but they were actually talking about me
Is it like obvious? I mean, I didn't stand up or anything
Did I miss something? I'm gonna go read
No, yeah
Yeah, apparently they've caught on to it that I'm wearing
Song ladies song too like there's
Men's song I guess I know. Yeah, they're called. What is it called banana hammock or something? I don't know I
Suppose look at them giggling away there in chat
How did they know these things like I didn't even stand up are you guys like recording things?
Somehow
Come on page I can't entertain I need someone to bounce off to talk to
Yeah, just give me one second. I'm just trying to change because I gotta put a different shirt on for this painting
Better watch it or they're gonna start saying stuff over in chat over there. I don't know which way
Say whatever you want
It's Canada drip
Let's have we dress in Canada well, I mean the dudes do anyways the women wear your beards
For the most part beards plaids and golf clubs
Down you got the Canadian beard down we just gotta work on the upper half of the level there. Yeah
No, it's not the guys that have the beard so it's the ladies
Sike has shown it. He's shown video of Paige with the beard. I mean, this is he's a traditional Canadian like a real Canadian, you know, like roots right in the ground.
I don't know where he went.
Gotti and Jay, I don't know.
Sike, if you there, drop the link. He did drop it just a little while ago, I think.
Maybe not.
Someone else get your ass up here for a sec because I got to go do something and I'll be right back in like 10
But I'm not leaving a thing up here by himself. He meant his underwear
Or where to pay
What kind of hair would would I get rain if I did get a to pay?
You'd have to get like all natural real it'd be they'd be like Indian hair unprocessed Indian hair
You'd have to get all natural hair be like five to a thousand, you know, so would it be straight?
Um well, I think that you'd go with like maybe a little volume
But nothing crazy on either end of the spectrum whether it be straight or curly right like right in between maybe
Okay
What was your hair like before probably just do that?
Oh, it's straight like I mean when I was a teen in that when you see pictures of me with long hair
It was like don't forget this was late 70s early 80s, right?
So like my hair was just straight and it was coming down like part in the middle
But it was straight just straight straight black hair
thin
Do you guys remember it was it Charlie's Angels the one where it's like there's it was a creepy thin man
And he's got like the hair that's like slicked on both sides and it's parted right in the middle
He's actually a really nice dude, but he might be like off putting at first. You know that guy
No
Psycharony drop the link drop the link come on
Folks one up
Bride of Chucky I never saw Bride of Chucky
Is that in your one or we're going back to like the original series ring
Did you ever see Bride of Chucky page
You know what I've seen pretty much every horror film like I like that kind of shit, right? So
Okay, from the original era, okay.
Fascinating.
That's weird that you say that, that I looked like a cop.
At a Pink Floyd show, I guess it was the first tour.
So when did they tour after their reformation?
I think it was like 84 or something like that.
So back in 84.
I went with the girl to one of the Floyd shows
and I didn't bring anything, man.
I was just, everything was hectic.
I didn't end up getting anything like to smoke, whatever.
And I went to ask these younger dudes, these teens,
because they were smoking and that's the first thing.
They're like, you're a cop, man.
You're totally a cop.
I'm not fucking giving you the shit.
I'm just like, oh.
in their defense most of the time it's like you know you're kind of like the
radar goes off when you know when someone's gonna ask you man walks up to
you and I get it I understand that but you know it was also the way I looked I
didn't look like like I was a little more I don't want to say hip just
You know, I was in 84.
No, this had to have been the second tour
because this was in the 90s, 91 or whatever, 92.
I was in my 20s already.
Anyways, I'm boring everybody.
Come on, Syke, drop the link.
You're not boring, you're just telling your stories.
It's nice to hear you talk as often as the rest of us,
you know?
Look everyone's abandoning
Well
Well, that's fucking sucks that means I got some work to do on myself as a person if people are leaving because of me
No, oh, sorry, sorry, they're making plans for for tomorrow and stuff
I thought they were saying, you know, like see you over at someone else's stream kind of thing
But never mind never mind
Let's just meet being a moron
But we're still boring them that part is true that part. I'm pretty sure
Thing can you take your shirt off I can but I won't
You have more hair on your nipples and you do your head
On my nipples? No, but I mean
I mean, I'm I'm Greek so I do have hair, but like I said before I'm I'm I very thin hair
I'm not like that really bushy kind of you know
your Mediterranean
Kind of hair thick and all that I don't have that. No, you can't see
No
Any other questions?
Not related to either of either of our bodies. I love that you threw that in there for me too.
No, I had I had had like full head of hair
Into my 20s until like, you know mid to late 20s. That's when I started noticing it was thinning like really thinning on the
uh hairline and then it was just evacuating my hair was evacuating oh i said thinning thinning
it was just getting thinner right like there were less hairs there than there were before
so it was starting to move at that point and then from there it just you know took like 10 years
and within 10 years it was back to over here it's just like why am i keeping my hair like just just go
Hey, God, you guess what? It's a secret
Baloney nipples I
Can see you with spiky hair thing. No
Ray bitching again, that's all he does right? Have you noticed that?
You know, that's what he's
cooking. You know, that's what
he's cooking. You know, that's
what he's cooking. You know, that's
Yeah, maybe I mean like I do I really got to just I got to deal with something quick and I'd like to get you don't get on this painting while we have majority of the people here so
Yeah, I just got it. I just got to go run out and check on the on some animals. Okay.